Jack Benny papers, 1930-1974
UCLA Library Special Collections
Jack Benny papers
1930-1974
134
UCLA Library Special Collections
58.5 linear feet (105 boxes, 6 cartons, and 9 oversize boxes)
Benjamin Kubelsky (1894-1974) was born in Chicago. He began his career as a violinist and turned to comedy in 1918. He was a successful vaudeville performer, actor and radio personality. The collection consists of radio and television scripts, photographs and production stills, personal and business records for the years 1935-1955 as well as magazines containing Benny articles, memorabilia, and awards.
Benny, Jack, 1894-1974
Conditions Governing Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance through our electronic paging system using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Jack Benny, 1967.
Gift of Joseph Fischer, 1970.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 709333
Biography
Benjamin Kubelsky was born on February 14, 1894 in Chicago; raised in Waukegan, Illinois; began career as a violinist; turned to comedy in 1918, first as Ben K. Benny, then Jack Benny; became successful vaudeville performer during the 1920s, playing the Palace in New York City; married Sadye Marks (professionally known as Mary Livingstone) in 1927; made film debut in 1929, radio debut in 1932, television debut in 1950; became concert artist in 1956 and made frequent fund-raising appearances; died in Los Angeles, December 26, 1974.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of materials relating to the career of comedian Jack Benny. Includes radio and television scripts, photographs and production stills, personal and business records for the years 1935-1955, magazines containing Benny articles, memorabilia, and awards.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Radio scripts (Boxes 1-42).
Television scripts (Boxes 42-57).
Tapes (Boxes 58-63).
Photographs (Boxes 64-79, 81).
Personal appearance materials 1948-1956 (Box 80).
Personal papers, correspondence, contracts (Boxes 82-98).
Serials (Boxes 90, 99).
Memorabilia, awards (Boxes 100-116).
Lucky Strike program scripts bound volumes (Boxes 117-120).
Benny, Jack, 1894-1974--Archives.; Comedians--United States--Archives.; Photographs.; Radio plays.; Television plays.
Container List
- Radio Scripts.
  - The Canada Dry Ginger Ale Program.
    General note
    (* = duplicate)
    - ., May 2, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., May 4, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., May 11, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., May 16, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., May 23, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., May 25, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., June 1, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., June 6, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., June 8, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., June 13, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., June 15, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., June 20, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., June 22, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., June 27, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., June 29, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., July 4, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., July 6, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., July 11, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., July 13, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., July 18, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., July 20, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., July 25, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., August 1, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., August 3, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., August 8, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ., August 9, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., August 15, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., August 17, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., August 22, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., August 24, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., August 29, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., August 31, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., September 5, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., September 7, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., September 12, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., September 14, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., September 19, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., September 21, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., September 26, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., September 28, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., October 3, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., October 5, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ., October 10, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., October 12, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., October 17, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., October 19, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., October 24, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., October 26, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., October 30, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., November 3, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., November 6, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., November 10, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., November 13, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., November 20, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., November 24, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., November 27, 1932. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ., December 1, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., December 4, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., December 8, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., December 11, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., December 15, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., December 18, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., December 22, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., December 29, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., January 1, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., January 5, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., January 8, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., January 12, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., January 15, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., January 19, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., January 22, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., January 26, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ., September 18, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., September 21, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., September 26, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., September 28, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., October 3, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., October 5, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., October 10, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., October 12, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., October 17, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., October 19, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., October 24, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., October 26, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., October 30, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., November 3, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., November 6, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., November 10, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., November 13, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - ., November 17, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., November 20, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., November 24, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., November 27, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., December 1, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., December 4, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., December 8, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., December 11, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., December 15, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., December 18, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., December 22, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - ., December 25, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., December 29, 1932. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., January 1, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., January 5, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., January 8, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., January 12, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., January 15, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., January 19, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., January 22, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - *., January 26, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Chevrolet Program.
    - ., March 3, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., March 10, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., March 17, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., March 24, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., March 31, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., April 7, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., April 14, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., April 21, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., April 28, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., May 5, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., May 12, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., May 19, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., May 26, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., June 2, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., June 9, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., June 16, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., June 23, 1933. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ., October 1, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ., December 4, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ., December 10, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ., December 17, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ., December 24, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ., December 31, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ., January 7, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ., January 14, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., January 21, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., January 28, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., February 4, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., February 11, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., February 18, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., February 25, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., March 4, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., March 11, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., March 18, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., March 25, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ., April 1, 1934. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - *., March 3, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - ., June 7, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - *., June 16, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - *., June 23, 1933. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - *., October 1, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ., October 8, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ., October 22, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ., October 29, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ., November 5, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ., November 12, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ., November 19, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ., November 26, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ., December 3, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - *., December 10, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - *., December 17, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - *., December 24, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - *., December 31, 1933. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - *., January 7, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., January 14, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., January 21, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., January 28, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., February 4, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., February 11, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., February 18, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., February 25, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., March 4, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., March 11, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., March 18, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., March 25, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - *., April 1, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The General Tire Program.
    - ., April 6, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., April 13, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., April 20, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., April 27, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., May 4, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., May 11, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., May 18, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., May 25, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., June 1, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., June 8, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., June 15, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., June 22, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., June 29, 1934. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ., July 6, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., July 13, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., July 20, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., July 27, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., August 3, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., August 10, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., August 17, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., August 24, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., August 31, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., September 7, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., September 14, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., September 21, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., September 28, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ., October 6, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - *., April 6, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - *., April 13, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - *., April 20, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - *., April 27, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - *., May 4, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - *., May 11, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - *., May 18, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - *., May 25, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - *., June 1, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - *., June 8, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - *., June 15, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - *., June 22, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - *., June 29, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - *., July 6, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - *., July 20, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - *., July 27, 1934. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - *., August 3, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - *., August 10, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - *., August 17, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - *., August 24, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - *., August 31, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - *., September 7, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - *., September 14, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - *., September 21, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - *., September 28, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - *., October 6, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - --Show Boat Program.., October 11, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - The Jello Program.
    * = duplicate
    - ., October 14, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., October 21, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., October 28, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., November 4, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., November 11, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., November 18, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., November 25, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., December 2, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., December 9, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., December 16, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., December 23, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., December 30, 1934. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., January 6, 1955. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ., January 13, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., January 20, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., January 27, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., February 3, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., February 10, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., February 17, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., February 24, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., March 3, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., March 10, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., March 17, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., March 24, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., March 31, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., April 7, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., April 14, 1935. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ., April 21, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., April 28, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., May 5, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., May 12, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., May 19, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., May 26, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., June 2, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., June 9, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., June 16, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., June 23, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., June 30, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., July 7, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., July 14, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ., September 29, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., October 6, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., October 13, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., October 20, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., October 27, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., November 3, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., November 10, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., November 17, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., November 24, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., December 1, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., December 6, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., December 15, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., December 22, 1935. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ., December 29, 1935. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., January 5, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., January 12, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., January 19, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., January 26, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., February 2, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., February 9, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., February 16, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., February 23, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., March 1, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., March 8, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., March 15, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., March 22, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ., March 29, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., April 5, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., April 12, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., April 19, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., April 26, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., May 3, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., May 10, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., May 17, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., May 24, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., May 31, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., June 7, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., June 14, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., June 21, 1936. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ., October 4, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., October 11, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., October 18, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., October 25, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., November 1, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., November 8, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., November 15, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., November 22, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., November 29, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., December 6, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., December 13, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., December 20, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., December 27, 1936. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., January 3, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., January 10, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., January 17, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., January 24, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., January 31, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., February 7, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., February 14, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., February 21, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., February 28, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., March 7, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., March 14, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., March 21, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., March 28, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., April 4, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., April 11, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., April 18, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., April 25, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., May 2, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., May 9, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., May 16, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., May 23, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., May 30, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., June 6, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., June 13, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., June 20, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., June 27, 1937. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ., October 3, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., October 10, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., October 17, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., October 24, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., November 7, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., November 14, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., November 21, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., November 28, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., December 5, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., December 12, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., December 19, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., December 26, 1937. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ., January 2, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ., January 9, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ., January 16, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ., January 23, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ., January 30, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ., February 6, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ., February 13, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ., February 20, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ., February 27, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ., March 6, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., March 13, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., March 20, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., March 27, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., April 3, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., April 10, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., April 17, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., April 24, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., May 1, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., May 8, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., May 15, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., May 22, 1938. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ., May 29, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - ., June 5, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - ., June 12, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - ., June 19, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - ., June 26, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - --Eddie Cantor Anniversary Dinner.., October 22, 1937. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - --Town Hall Tonite.., December 22, 1937. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - --Interview with Bill Morrow and Ed Beloin.., January 7, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - --Dale Armstrong Interview.., January 25, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - --Beverly Hills Chamber of Commerce Dinner.., January 31, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - --Maxwell House, Good News of 1938.., February 17, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - --American Legion Anniversary Broadcast.., March 15, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - ., October 2, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - ., October 9, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - ., October 16, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - ., October 23, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - ., October 30, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - ., November 6, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - ., November 13, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - ., November 20, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - ., November 27, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - ., December 4, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - ., December 11, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - ., December 18, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - ., December 25, 1938. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - ., January 1, 1939. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - ., January 8, 1939. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - ., January 15, 1939. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - ., January 22, 1939. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - ., January 29, 1939. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - ., February 5, 1939. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - ., February 12, 1939. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - ., February 19, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ., February 26, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ., March 5, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ., March 12, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ., March 19, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ., March 26, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ., April 2, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ., April 9, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ., April 16, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ., April 23, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ., April 30, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ., May 7, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ., May 14, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ., May 21, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ., May 28, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - ., June 4, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - ., June 11, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - ., June 18, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - ., June 25, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - ., October 8, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - ., October 15, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - ., October 22, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - ., October 29, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - ., November 5, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - ., November 12, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - ., November 19, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - ., November 26, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - ., December 3, 1939. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - ., January 14, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - ., January 21, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - ., January 28, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - ., February 4, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - ., February 11, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - ., February 18, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - ., February 25, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - ., March 3, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ., March 10, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ., March 17, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ., March 24, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ., March 31, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ., April 7, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ., April 14, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ., April 21, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ., April 28, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - ., May 5, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - ., May 12, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - ., May 19, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - ., May 26, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - ., June 2, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - ., June 9, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - ., June 16, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - --Children's Home and Nursery Program.., August 13, 1939. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - --Salvation Army Program.., December 16, 1939. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - --Radio Guide Sketch.., February 10, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - --Kate Smith Hour.., April 26, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - --Fred Allen Show.., June 19, 1940. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - ., October 6, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - ., October 13, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - ., October 20, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - ., October 27, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - ., November 3, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)